Guide to the Ipas Records, 1965-2020; 1965-ongoing RL.00617
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Africa Programs, 1973-2012; 23 boxes
  - Ghana Programs, 1992-2010
    - Overview of Ipas in Ghana Reports 92-06; Ipas Ghana 93-97; Reports/Proposals/Meetings 97-04; Abortion Law/Policy 99; Team Meeting Minutes 99-00; Country Strat Plan 00-04; Background 01; PAC Case Study in Ghana 01; Strategic Plan 01-05; Post Abortion Care (PAC) Reports 01-05; AB research report 03; Trip Reports 03-04; Misc Reports 03-06; Health Service AB plan 04; 2004 Activities; Mtg Notes 05; AB Assessment 05; Health Sector Report 05; Baseline Assessment of Regional Hospitals 05; Abortion Doctoral Thesis 05; Ghana Comms FY05; CAC Assessment 05; Values Clarification Workshop – June '06 VCAT; Plan & Proposal '06; Abortion Care Assessment FY 06; Social Security Law, Workmen's Compensation, Labour Act 06; Monthly Reports 06-07; Workshop Reports 06; Ipas Ghana History FY06; R3M partners' proposals 06; Background documents 06; Trip reports for Ghana FY 06-07; Ghana Misc 06-07; Ghana M&E 06-07; IPAS GHANA in the News 07; R3M Champions 07; R3m Research Study IPAS-WHO FY07; M. Luke SOGON Keynote 07; CAC Research Project FY07; RMMM Partners Agreement 07; RMMM 07-08; M&E indicators 07-09; Ghana Team Mtg 08; Midwife Council Proposal 08; Ghana Pre-service Project 08; Nurses + Midwives Council Proposal FY09; Planning 09; RMMM FY09-10; BMMM Donor Proposal FY10, 1992-2006 (Box 181)
    - 8 Ipas Ghana posters with messaging about safe abortion care and the dangers of abortion stigma (Box 208)
  - Uganda Programs, 1992-2004
    - Comms 92-96; trip reports 94-00; WHO 95-96; donor proposals/reports 95-98; program history 95-00; background 95-01; Achurobwe ICR 96; contracts 96; field proposals/reports 96-00; Achurobwe 97-98; comms 97-98; PRIME working files 97-99; midwives study 97; ODA concept paper 98; papers 98-99; comms 99-01; Rose Nalwadda ICR 00; quality of care mtg 00; EDF microprojects 00; Pathfinder collaboration 00; private sector training 00; RH stakeholders 00; DISH working files 00-01; CARE 00-01; team mtg notes 00-01; country plan 00-04 (Box 52)
    - Uganda: GTZ proposal 01, NGO reg, TOT, UPMA proposal, planning 02 Tanzania: Background 90-00, assessment/eval tools workshop 94, country summaries, correspondence. 95-00, Tanz III 95-97 working files, AVSC/Ipas collaboration and assessment tools 95-98, Field reports 97, AVSC/Ipas meetings 97-00, Dr. Urassa 97-99, URT PAC eval 98, AVSC/Ipas 98-00 working files; AVSC/Ipas APHA paper; AVSC subagreement 99; National expansion program working files 99; MOH 00; PRIME 01, 1995-2001 (Box 53)
  - Africa Regional Files, 1989-2007
    - Lilliane Toumi 83-96; Blumenthal 89-90; Jan Bradley correspondence 89-90; Conference on Adolescent Health 92; Francophone 92; private mission hospitals 92; college of surgeons mtg 92; MWIA congress 93; training numbers 93-95; Lisa Bohmer regional rep 94; regional trainers workshop 94; African Medical Association Conference 94-95; E&S Africa PAC proposal 94-96; ministers mtg 95; regional RH workshop 95; PAFP TOT 95; Bohmer correspondence 95-96; regional correspondence 95-99; advocacy Rogo 96; E&S Africa project working files 95-97; Policy Project 96-97; Aloo-Obunga reg rep 96-98; standards correspondence 96-98; UNFPA/CEDPA adolescent mtg 97; E&S Africa strat mtg 97; CMA 97; PRIME ECSACON 97; E&S Africa working files 97-99; policy project 97-98; CAMAS 97-98; ECSCOGS 97-99, 1983-1989 (Box 54)
    - Nairobi regional office 98; E&S Africa Standards document 98; E&S Africa donor correspondence; PRIME 99; Partnership ideas 99; internal reports 99; Khama Rogo - medical advisor 99-01; Africa strategy planning meeting 00; objectives/progress 00; fundraising 00-03; Pop Council mtg 01; planning 01; cluster mtg minutes 02; planning 02; planning 03; planning documents 03; Addis regional unsafe abortion mtg 03; post-Addis follow-up 03; policy planning 04; Sida proposal 04-07, 1998-2007 (Box 55)
    - Botswana correspondence 91-97, PAC training 01, MVA workshop 02; Cameroon 99; Egypt 02; Lesotho 96; Malawi working files 94-96; Swaziland 01; Zaire trip reports 87-91, Pop Council correspondence 89-90, correspondence 90, correspondence Martin 90-91, proposal/reports 90-91, general correspondence 89-90; Zambia trip reports 87-92, donor proposals/report 91-93, correspondence 93-96, reports 94-95, Zimbabwe donor proposal 95-96, correspondence 96, country summaries 95-99, trip reports 89-92, correspondence 89-93, research project 90-91, contract 91, TOT 91, field reports 90-92, blocked funds 93-95, UNFPA 96, TOT 96, ZNFPC 96-98, trip reports 96-97; planning 96-98; background 96-01, 1987-2001 (Box 56)
    - Africa Mission Trip report 1987, Africa regional trainers mtg 94, MWIA conference 94, regional docs 00-03, Ethiopia posters, Ghana misc 94-95, Ghana strategy mtg 01, Ghana "Linking Research to Action" mtg 01, Ghana CAC assessment 05, Kenya funders 90-91, Kenya MVA Eval 92, Kenya donor reports 92-95, Malawi corresp 00, Nigeria donor reports 81-93, Nigeria donor proposals/reports 81-93, Nigeria MVA training 90-91, Nigeria Brookman-Amissah reception 02, Tanzania misc 94-96, Zaire 87-91, Zambia donor reports 90-92, Zambia field reports 91, Zimbabwe MVA trainings 91-94, South Africa misc 01-02, 1987-2002 (Box 108)
    - Benin FY07; Burkina Faso FY07; Kenya MVA Training in Kenya 93-94; Kenya PAC training FY 97; Kenya Kenyatta Hospital 99; Kenya Liz update to BOD FY00; Kenya Talking Points FY00; Kenya MVA Distribution 05; Mali FY07; Mozambique/Medical Abortion Research FY05-06; Mozambique 07-08; Mozambique FY07-09; Mozambique Safe AB proposal 08; Uganda Int'l Women & Health Mtg FY94; Uganda 05; Zambia 08-09; Zambia OR study 09; Zambia Sida Logframe FY10; Zambia 10-11; Africa Regional 96-12: E&S Regional Strategy FY96; Donor Proposal FY96; REDSO/Policy Project FY97; Violence Against Women FY99-00; Trip Report FY01; PAC in Francophone 02; NY Presentation on Int'l AB policy 03; Ipas Program Unit Meetings FY 04-06; Ghana Report COC 05; Africa Region RH + abortion articles, paper, estimates FY 05, Donor Potential 06; PPD Reporting 06; FIGO rights workshop 06; P&Rs & workplans 06-07; Regional Performance Overview 07; SAC Indicators Workshop 07; Indicators Workshop SDP Data 07; Reporting Requirements FY 07; MA Background 07-08; Meetings – Conferences 07-09; Office Leases 07-10; 3rd Africa Conf on SH&R 08; Ipas BOD Orientation 08; Desk Retreat 08; Francophone Trip 08; Regional DFID Logframe FY08; Proposal – safe ab care 08; Chrono-Direct 08-09; ARD Reports/Minutes FY08-09; Proposals & Reports 08-12; Annual Country Planning FY09; Africa Contracts 09; Donor Discussions 09; Sida 09; Country Profiles FY09; Engender Health Coord Workshop 09; Fragile States 09; Regional Retreat 09; Best Practices Mtg 09; Staff Trips to Africa 10; Region Planning FY10l Regional job descriptions 10; Fragile States FY10; Directors Strat planning 10; DFID/PMDUP 10; OPS Manual Presentation 10; Uganda/Malawi/Zambia proposal 10-12, 1993-2012 (Box 179)
  - Africa Alliance, 2000-2010
    - Africa Alliance structure planning 00-01; office team minutes 00-03; research 01-02; donor proposals/reports 00-02; internal reports 01-03; small grants 01-03; Africa Ipas map 02; planning/objectives 02; presentation to Ipas BOD 02; fundraising 02-03; trip reports 02-03; donor World Bank 02-03; Euro donor 02-03; Kenya baseline study 03; Mozambique 02-03; training reports/schedules 03; regional summaries 02-03; CMHW curriculum 03; Kenya maendelo project 03; Addis meeting 03; Addis mtg statements 03; donor proposals/reports 02-05; Workplans 03; Brookman-Amissah visit NC 03; donor visits 03; Dr. Mwalili 03; Braam 03; Zimbabwe 03; Kenya planning 03; AA relocation issues 03; 63iii 03; program reviews 03; comms 03; planning/budgets 03; Kenya abortion debate 04; planning/monitoring 04; donor JICA 04; Tanzania 04; Namibia 04; Kenya 04; Kenya TeenWeb lessons 04; diagram structure 04; internal reports 04; CIDA magnitude study 04, 2000-2003 (Box 57)
    - AAIPF Contract 04; Dr. Brookman-Amissah 04; FY05 individual workplans 04-05; General Notes FY04-05; Alliance conference participation 04-05; Mgmnt cycle/P&R FY 04-06; Mozambique FY04-06; Alliance conference participation 04-05; Mgmnt Cycle/P&R FY 04-06; Country Program: Botswana FY 04-06; Donors: Sida 04-07; Donors/FINIDA: (04-07) Proposal; Donor Advocacy 05; FY05 planning/team workplans; Donor report 05; FY05 Conference mats; Country Program: Zimbabwe FY05-09; Office/Staff info 06; Donors: World Bank (proposal submitted spring 2005); Zambia; Alliance Planning FY06; Alliance – Roles + Resp 05; AA Overview FY 08; Contracts 08-10; AA staff mtg 10; Planning Retreat 10; AA Security plan 10; Ethiopia 92-10: Newspaper 92; Program History 92-00; Proposal – Sustainability pilot FY96; Sustainability Plan 96; Yamamu grant 00; Trip Reports 00; Status of Women Presentation 00; UNFPA Project Document 00; Consultant Proposals Legal scan 00; 5-year Mobilization proposal/reports 00-02; Country workplan 00-02; PAC Factsheets 01; Community Abortion Research 02; Donors/Netherlands Embassy: Proposal 03-06; Mgmnt Cycle/P&R fY04-05; Dutch Contracts 04-06; Netherlands Phase I Interim Reports (2004-2006); Launch Plus 05; Grant Letter 05-06; Donor Reports FY 05-08; Donor Reports FY05-08; Donor Proposal 05-08; Activity Monitoring FY 06; Netherlands Interim Report (October 2005-March 2006 final copy) 06; MVA Registration 06/2007; Netherlands Phase II Proposal (2006-2009); Netherlands Phase II Contract (2006-2009); 3 Year Plans 07-09; Dutch contract amendment FY 08; Capacity Assessment 08; Nat'l Magnitude Presentation 08; FY08 planning; Misc Program Notes FY09; Consultant Proposal – CAC Assessment 10; Ipas Ethiopia Contracts; Eval Phase 2 Netherlands FY10; Nigeria 00-10: Ipas PAC history FY00; PAC Training Reports 01; MVA Reg 03; Eval of Ipas-Nigeria 04; Donor Reports FY04-05; Uche Ekenna's files 04-06; In the News – Ipas Nigeria FY 04-07; PAC Donor Report 05; Donor PAC report FY05; PAC – Safe Motherhood; FY 06; PAC Scale-up SIDA report 06; Ipas Nigeria History 06; Proposals/Reports (Donor) 06-07; Supporting Docs FY06-07; PAC Trg Program 07; Contract Agreements FY07; Strategic Plan 07-09; Donor Proposal/Report 07-09; PAC Donor Proposal 07-09; Donor Proposal/Report 07-10; Donor Proposal/ Report 07-10; Donor Letter 08; Contracts FY08; BOD-Report 08; Plan-IT 08-09; Env Scan FY 09; Team Mtg FY 09; TSDI FY09; Nigeria Planning FY09; Advocacy & RH Workshop; Logframe suboutputs FY10, 2004-2010 (Box 178)
- Chronological Files, 1974-2006; 7 boxes
  - 1974 (June-December), 1975, 1976 (missing June), 1977-1979 (Box 58)
  - 1980, 1982, 1984 (January-June), 1985 (March-April), 1986 (July, September, October), 1987 (March-November), 1988 (May, October, November), 1989 (January, April, May, September-December), 1990 (Box 59)
  - 1991-1993, 1994 (January-June) (Box 60)
  - 1995-1996, 1997 (January-June) (Box 61)
  - 1997 (July-December), 1998-2000, 2001 (January-May) (Box 62)
  - 2001 (June-November), 2002-2003, 2004 (January-June) (Box 63)
  - July 2004 - March 2006 (each month) (Box 107)
- Program Files and Internal Documentation, 1970-2011; 32 boxes
  - Ipas Resource Center Archives: APLIC Resources, Pre-Ipas abortion study 1970, Correspondence, database keyword list, user services, library scimate, Popline, APLIC notebook, SECS document collection notebook; database CDs (Box 64)
  - Ipas Internal Trainings and Workshops 1991-2002: Ipas Public Speaking Workshop 1991, Strategic Planning Notebook 1997-1998, Adolescent Teen Pregnancy -- fact sheets, article, and PP presentation 1997-2000, Challenging the Conventional Wisdom: Lessons Learned from Postabortion Family Planning Research 1999, Ipas Matrix Management 1999, Consensus Decision-Making Workshop 2001, Country Team Leader: Training Workshop 2000, "It's OK to Disagree!" Conflict Management Workshop 2000; Reproductive Health for Refugees 2000, Microsoft Outlook Workshops 2001, Réunion Regional de América Latina y el Caribe 2001, Building Capacity for Training Launch and Scale-up: A Workshop for Staff and Lead Trainers 2002, Country Team Leaders' Meeting: "Working and Learning Together" 2002, From Planning to Printing: A Guide to Ipas Publications 2002, Global Event Monitoring System training 2002 (Box 69)
  - Ipas Internal Trainings and Workshops 2003-2004: Fundraising at Ipas 2003, Ipas Program Management Initiative 2003, Common Sense Rules for Workplace Behavior, Level One Leadership Training Series 2004 (Box 70)
  - External Conferences attended by Ipas staff and Ipas sponsored-conferences for external audiences: World Federation: Women's Issues Planning Group, Ankara, Turkey, 16-18 Apr 1986; Planned Parenthood Federation of America: Annual Meeting, Boston, MA, 19-22 Nov. 1987; Reproductive Health Technologies Meeting, Reproductive Health Technologies Project, Washington, D.C., 9-May-89; Meeting Women's Needs for Post-Abortion Family Planning, Bellagio, Italy, 1-5 Feb. 1993; NGO Forum, The Population Institute, Cairo, Egypt 5-13 Sep. 1994; Informe de la Conferencia Internacional sobre la Poblacion y el Desarrollo, UN, Cairo, Egypt, 5-13 Sep. 1994; FIGO Montréal 1994, Montreal, Canada, 24-30 Sep. 1994; Inter-Agency Symposium on Reproductive Health in Refugee Situations, UNHCR, UNFPA, UNICEF, WHO, Geneva, Switz. 28-30 Jun. 1995; How and When: A Medical Abortion Update, Preparing Your Clinic for Medical Abortion, National Abortion Federation, Washington, D.C., 31 Mar. 1996; National Council for International Health, Arlington, VA, 25-27 Jun. 1998; Technical Update on Gender-Based Violence and Reproductive Health/HIV, IGWG, Oct-99; High-level Intergovernmental Meeting to Review Regional Implementation of the Beijing Platform for Action, Economic and Social Commission for Asia and the Pacific, Bangkok, Thailand, 26-29 Oct. 1999; Cuba Congress, ALAMES, Cuba, 3-4 Jul. 2000; Choices for Women with Unplanned Pregnancies, Division of Family Planning and Population, Bangkok, Thailand, 6 Jul. 2000; FIGO 2000, Washington, D.C., 3-8 Sep. 2000; Meeting on Maternal Mortality Surveillance, PAHO, Washington, D.C., 16-17 Oct. 2000; Reunion sobre la Vigilancia Epidepmiologica de la Mortalidad Materna, WHO, PAHO, Washington, D.C., 16-17 Oct. 2000, Workshop on Maternal Mortality Epidemiological Surveillance, WHO, PAHO, Washington, D.C., 16-17 Oct. 2000; Conferencia Regional Sobre Programas de Atencion Post-Aborto en América Latina Ministerio de Salud Publica y Aisstencia Social, Guatemala City,21-22 Jun. 2001; Unwanted Pregnancy and Abortion: Public Health Challenges in Latin America and the Caribbean, Instituto Nacional de Salud Publica, Cuernavaca, Mexico, 12-14 Nov. 2001; 45th All India Congress of Obstretics and Gynaecology, FOGSI, Bhubaneswar, India, 6-9 Jan. 2002; Mujeres, Violencia y Salud, Ipas, SSA, Mexico City, MX, 8-12 Apr. 2002; Photos, National Conference and 29th Annual General Meeting of the OBGYN Society of Bangladesh, Bangladesh, 2002; Action to Reduce Maternal Mortality in Africa, Economic Commission for Africa, Addis Ababa, Ethiopia, 5-7 Mar. 2003; Advancing Women's Access to Safe Abortion: An International Strategy Wkshp, Ipas, Chapel Hill, NC, 27-30 Apr. 2004; Advancing Women's Access to Safe Abortion: A Regional Strategy Wkshp, Ipas, Nairobi, Kenya, 28-30 June 2004 (Box 71-73)
  - Vacuum Aspiration literature, 1989 and 2003; Core donor proposals and reports, 1987-2003; Rebecca Cook Program of Research, 1994-1997; Communications Unit, 1989-1998; Reprints of articles by Ipas staff in peer-review journals (Box 84)
  - Medical Abortion (MA): Miso background 1994, Methotrexate 1995, PP medical abortion 1996, Mifepristone slides 1996, MA background 1996-1998, Mifepristone background 1997-2003, RHTP mtg 1998, Miso lit review 2000, Safety and efficacy 2001, RH Alliance Europe 2001, Legality/availability/cost 2001-2002, PATH 2001-2003, MA Table 2002, MA Task Force meetings and planning 2001-2004, Safe Access Mtg 2004 (Box 85)
  - PRIME and PRIME II working files, 1997-2003 (Box 86)
  - PRIME and PRIME II reports, 1995-2001 (Box 87)
  - Global and Cross-Regional Programs and Projects: Infection prevention 1987-1993, Working with women's groups 1990, MVA activities 1991, Harrison McKay's trips 1992, World Health Organization clinical guidelines 1992, Women's Perspectives Task Force 1992, Interconnection newsletter 1992-1996, Estimating MVA instruments, Indicators of institutionalization, Evaluation instruments 1992, Bellagio Conference working files 1993, International Women's Health meeting Uganda 1993, PAFP curriculum 1995-1996, Jose David Ortiz 1996, Prevention of Maternal Mortality conference 1996, Mid-level providers 1993-2002 (including ICM conferences), FCI unsafe abortion guide, Programs planning 1998, PAC-PIP working files 1998, 2nd trimester work 1999, UNFPA refugees 1999-2001, P. Blumenthal's presentation at Agra conference 2000, Adolescents 2001 and 2003, Regional Directors retreat 2002, COBAC 2002, program planning 2003, World Health Organization Strategic Assessment 2004 (Box 94)
  - Media Files 1992-2006: Kenya 92-04, Media training 01, media resources 01, PAC Consortium 01-04, PAC Comms Task Force 01-04, S.A. mid-level mtg 02, Addis Meeting working files 03, Hipnet 03, APHA 03, Feminist Majority Fdn 03, Comms strategy 03, Kenya partnership exchange 03, Panos collaboration 03, Doug Gould 03, Nicaragua 03, video distribution 03, Panos commissioning ltrs 03-04, Portraits piece 03, Ipas messages 04, Nepal 04, Doug Gould 04, IFP presentation 04, APHA 04, Ext Comms strategy 04, March for Women's Lives files 04, Catholics for Free Choice Mex City 04, Kenya 04-05, Kings county 05, MVA launch partner presentation 05, Doug Gould 05, L Maguire Ethiopia 05, Circle of Friendship 05, EC 05, Africa country directors media training 05, Treaty Monitoring committees 05, media planning 05, human rights work 05, El Salvador 05, Charlotte paper op-ed 05, Comms/Dev retreat 06, Doug Gould 06, Board visioning 06, Bolivia 06, Media 06, Ayotte v PP 06, UN Millenium project 06, sex selection abortion 06 (Box 95)
  - Ipas Internal Trainings and Workshops, 2001-2005: Genderized: Ipas' Gender Workshop (n.d.); "It's Okay to Disagree": Ipas Workshop on Managing Conflict 2001; Ipas Monitoring and Evaluation Guide: Ipas Africa Staff Meeting 2001; Workshop on Consensus Decision-Making 2001; Building Capacity for Training Launch and Scale-Up 2002; Effective Training Courses (TOT1) 2002; MVA Training for Miscarriage Management 2003; MVA Plus Global Launch 2004; Ipas Project Management Workshop 2004; Ipas Project Management Workshop: Africa Region 2004; Ipas Taller de Gestion de Proyectos 2004; Intranet training Workshop 2005; Alliance for Justice 2005 (Box 110)
  - Ipas Internal trainings and workshops: Challenging the Conventional Wisdom: Lessons Learned from Postabortion Family Planning Research, Nov 1999 Expanding Reach and Impact, September 12-23, 2005 TSDI Global Workshop, September 25-29, 2006 Planning & Budget Process Redesign Project, January 2007 Leadership Development Workshop, January 16, 2007 Country Directors Meeting, October 1-5, 2007 R&E Global Meeting, September 24-Oct 5, 2007 SAC Indicators Workshop, March 21, 2007 Planning for a Sustainable Supply of MVA Instruments: A Workshop for Program Managers, March 7-9, 2007 Ipas Providers as Advocates for Safe Abortion Care, April 29, 2008 Ipas Media Training, May 22-23, 2008 Abortion VCAT Facilitation workshop for TSDI and Consultants, September 15, 2008 Ipas Logframe Workshop, December 10-11, 2008 TSDI Global Meeting, September 8-12, 2008 Facilitating Policy Reform through Advocacy: A skills-building Workshop for Change-Agents, April 13-17, 2009 Providers as Advocates for Safe Abortion Care Facilitation Workshop, June 9, 2009 Expanding Access to Medical Abortion through Pharmacies, Chemist Shops and Medicine Sellers, June 1-2, 2009 (Box 131)
  - External Conferences attended by Ipas staff and Ipas sponsored-conferences for external audiences: Antiprogestin Drugs: Ethical, Legal and Medical Issues, Arlington, VA, 6-7 December 1991; Honoring our Commitments, US Implementation of the ICPD, Washington, DC, 21-22 February 1996; 3rd Reproductive Health Priorities conference, Western Cape, South Africa, 19-22 August 1997; Roundtable on Reproductive Rights and Implementation of Reproductive Health Programmes, Kampala, Uganda, 22-25 June 1998; Confounding the Critics: Cairo, 5 years on, Cocoyoc Morelos, Mexico, 15-18 November 1998; International Forum of Parliamentarians on ICPD Review, The Hague, Netherlands, 4-6 February 1999; NGO Forum and Youth Fora ICPD + 5, The Hague, Netherlands, 6-7 February 1999; ICPD+5: Fulfilling the Commitment, The Hague, Netherlands, 8-12 February 1999; APHA Annual Meeting, Atlanta, GA 21-25 October 2001; Global Health Council, Annual Conference, Washington DC, 28-31 May 02; Initiative Francophone Régionale: Soins Aprés Avortement, Conférence Régionale, Dakar, Senegal, 4-7 March 2002; Global Health Council, Annual Conference, Washington Dc, 28-31 May 2002; APHA Annual Meeting, Philadelphia, PA, 9-13 November 2002; APHA, Annual Meeting, San Francisco, CA, 16-19 November 2003; XV International AIDS Conference, Bangkok, Thailand, 11-16 July 2004; APHA Annual Meeting, Washington DC, 6-10 November 2004; Second Meeting on Abortion Law Reform Strategy in LAC, Mexico City; 21-22 November 2004; Expanding Capacity for a Safe Abortion Movement at the Highest Level, Circle of Friends Workshop, Nairobi, Kenya, 23-25 February 2005; Global Health Council, Annual Conference, Washington DC, 31 May - 3 June 2005; U.S. Global Engagement on Sexual and Reproductive Health and Rights: Strategic Messaging Meeting, Washington DC, 21 July 2005; Réunion de Expertas sobre Alternativas de Atención en el Sector Salud a Mujeres Sobrevivientes de Violencia Sexual, Washington DC, 2-4 August 2005; 3rd Asia Pacific Conference on Reproductive and Sexual Health, Petaling Jaya, Malaysia, 17-21 November 2005; 3rd reunion sobre las Políticas del Aborto en América Latina, Montevideo, Uruguay, 27-28 November 2005; Dialogue on: Role of National MR Program for the Promotion of Sexual and Reproductive Health and Rights in Bangladesh, Dhaka, Bangladesh, 19 February 2006; Outcomes for Advocacy Workshop, New York City, 5 December 2006 (Box 111-112)